{
   
   
    "q1":{
            "question" : "1. Why so JavaScript and Java have similar name?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "JavaScript is a stripped-down version of Java",
                "option2" : "They both originated on the island of Java",
                "option3" : "JavaScript's syntax is loosely based on Java's",
                "option4" : "None of the above"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            },
       
    "q2":{
            "question" : "2. Using AJAX we can made our web page.",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Easy to connect web page with server",
                "option2" : "More dynamic",
                "option3" : "More interactive and faster",
                "option4" : "None of the above"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            }, 
    
    "q3":{
            "question" : "3. What combination of technologies gives AJAX its name?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Atlas and XML",
                "option2" : "Asynchronous JavaScript and XML",
                "option3" : "Autonomic Computing and DHTML",
                "option4" : "ASP and XAML"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            },
    
    "q4":{
            "question" : "4.  When a user views a page containing a JavaScript program, which machine actually executes the script?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "The Web server",
                "option2" : "A central machine deep within Netscape's corporate offices",
                "option3" : "The User's machine running a Web browser",
                "option4" : "None of the above"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            },
    
    "q5":{
            "question" : "5. AJAX made popular by",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Microsoft",
                "option2" : "Google",
                "option3" : "IBM",
                "option4" : "un Microsystem"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            },
    
    "q6":{
            "question" : "6. The XMLHttpRequest object can be disabled via browser settings.",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "false",
                "option2" : "true",
                "option3" : "can't possible",
                "option4" : "none"
                },
            "answer" : "1"
            },
     "q7":{
            "question" : "7. What does the < noscript> tag do?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Describes certain low-budget movies.",
                "option2" : "Enclose text to be displayed by non-JavaScript browsers.",
                "option3" : "Prevents scripts on the page from executing.",
                "option4" : "none"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            },
       
    "q8":{
            "question" : "8. Which one of these libraries does not include Drag and Drop support:",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "GWT",
                "option2" : "Dojo",
                "option3" : "YUI",
                "option4" : "Script.aculo.us"
                },
            "answer" : "1"
            }, 
    
    "q9":{
            "question" : "9. Which Javascript library listed below comes with an Accordion Widget?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Rico",
                "option2" : "JQuery",
                "option3" : "Prototype",
                "option4" : "YUI"
                },
            "answer" : "1"
            },
    
    "q10":{
            "question" : "10. Script.aculo.us is:",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "a javascript effects library",
                "option2" : "a cross browser compatibility library",
                "option3" : "used for static web content",
                "option4" : "an alternative to Prototype"
                },
            "answer" : "1"
            }
}
    
   
   
   
  